{
    "MCQ": [
        {
            "question": "who are you?",
            "choices": {
                "A": "me",
                "B": "them",
                "C": "they"
            },
            "answer": "A",
            "num_correct": 1,
            "num_wrong": 1,
            "state": 1
        }
    ],
    "FRQ": [
        {
            "question": "je vous prie d'accepter l'expression de mes salutations",
            "answer": "I beg you to accept my goodbyes",
            "num_correct": 0,
            "num_wrong": 0,
            "state": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "avaler",
            "answer": "to swallow",
            "num_correct": 0,
            "num_wrong": 0,
            "state": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "avoir faim",
            "answer": "to be hungry",
            "num_correct": 0,
            "num_wrong": 0,
            "state": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "bouffer",
            "answer": "to eat",
            "num_correct": 0,
            "num_wrong": 0,
            "state": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "commander",
            "answer": "to order",
            "num_correct": 0,
            "num_wrong": 0,
            "state": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "consommer",
            "answer": "to consume",
            "num_correct": 0,
            "num_wrong": 0,
            "state": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "d\u00e9couper",
            "answer": "to cut up",
            "num_correct": 0,
            "num_wrong": 0,
            "state": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "d\u00e9geler",
            "answer": "to defrost",
            "num_correct": 0,
            "num_wrong": 0,
            "state": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "d\u00e9graisser",
            "answer": "to degrease",
            "num_correct": 0,
            "num_wrong": 0,
            "state": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "d\u00e9guster",
            "answer": "to taste",
            "num_correct": 0,
            "num_wrong": 0,
            "state": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "dig\u00e9rer",
            "answer": "to digest",
            "num_correct": 0,
            "num_wrong": 0,
            "state": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "donner \u00e0 manger",
            "answer": "to feed",
            "num_correct": 0,
            "num_wrong": 0,
            "state": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "\u00e9goutter",
            "answer": "to drain",
            "num_correct": 0,
            "num_wrong": 0,
            "state": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "emporter",
            "answer": "to deliver",
            "num_correct": 0,
            "num_wrong": 0,
            "state": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "\u00e9plucher",
            "answer": "to peel",
            "num_correct": 0,
            "num_wrong": 0,
            "state": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "faire blanchir",
            "answer": "to blanche",
            "num_correct": 0,
            "num_wrong": 0,
            "state": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "faire bouillir",
            "answer": "to boil",
            "num_correct": 0,
            "num_wrong": 0,
            "state": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "faire chauffer",
            "answer": "to heat",
            "num_correct": 0,
            "num_wrong": 0,
            "state": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "faire cuire",
            "answer": "to cook",
            "num_correct": 0,
            "num_wrong": 0,
            "state": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "faire les courses",
            "answer": "to go food shopping",
            "num_correct": 0,
            "num_wrong": 0,
            "state": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "faire r\u00e9duire",
            "answer": "to reduce (liquid)",
            "num_correct": 0,
            "num_wrong": 0,
            "state": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "garnir",
            "answer": "to garnish",
            "num_correct": 0,
            "num_wrong": 0,
            "state": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "go\u00fbter",
            "answer": "to taste",
            "num_correct": 0,
            "num_wrong": 0,
            "state": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "grignoter",
            "answer": "to nibble, snack",
            "num_correct": 0,
            "num_wrong": 0,
            "state": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "griller",
            "answer": "to grill",
            "num_correct": 0,
            "num_wrong": 0,
            "state": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "m\u00e2cher",
            "answer": "to chew",
            "num_correct": 0,
            "num_wrong": 0,
            "state": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "manger sain",
            "answer": "to eat healthy",
            "num_correct": 0,
            "num_wrong": 0,
            "state": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "m\u00e9langer",
            "answer": "to mix",
            "num_correct": 0,
            "num_wrong": 0,
            "state": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "nourrir",
            "answer": "to feed",
            "num_correct": 0,
            "num_wrong": 0,
            "state": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "p\u00e9trir",
            "answer": "to knead",
            "num_correct": 0,
            "num_wrong": 0,
            "state": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "poivrer",
            "answer": "to pepper",
            "num_correct": 0,
            "num_wrong": 0,
            "state": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "pr\u00e9parer",
            "answer": "to prepare",
            "num_correct": 0,
            "num_wrong": 0,
            "state": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "saisir",
            "answer": "to season",
            "num_correct": 0,
            "num_wrong": 0,
            "state": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "saler",
            "answer": "to salt",
            "num_correct": 0,
            "num_wrong": 0,
            "state": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "saupoudrer",
            "answer": "to sprinkle with",
            "num_correct": 0,
            "num_wrong": 0,
            "state": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "sauter",
            "answer": "to saut\u00e9",
            "num_correct": 0,
            "num_wrong": 0,
            "state": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "verser",
            "answer": "to pour",
            "num_correct": 0,
            "num_wrong": 0,
            "state": 0
        }
    ],
    "SAQ": [
        {
            "question": "what is the meawning of life",
            "answer": "hi",
            "num_correct": 2,
            "num_wrong": 1,
            "state": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "what is the meawning of life",
            "answer": "<pad> meawning, life, meawning</s>",
            "num_correct": 0,
            "num_wrong": 1,
            "state": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "what is the meawning of life",
            "answer": "<pad> meawning, life, meawning</s>",
            "num_correct": 0,
            "num_wrong": 1,
            "state": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "what is the meawning of life",
            "answer": " meawning, life, meawning",
            "num_correct": 0,
            "num_wrong": 0,
            "state": 0
        }
    ]
}